穿过了小巷后的古街
Inside the archaic lane I passed by
青墙旁你遥望夕阳斜
Saw you were glowing in the sunlight
只因是不经意的一瞥
The way you and I caught at first sight
扰乱我思绪不舍昼夜
Disturbed my mind every single night
想化作庄周变成蝴蝶
Wish I could fly like a butterfly
驾青云穿过繁枝茂叶
Anytime I'll be right by your side
纵然是群山层层叠叠
My love's as river deep mountain high
也无心在此流连停歇
There ain't no way I can take my time
将相思寄明月
Lay under the moonlight
期盼你能察觉
Pray you not to think twice
将你写作诗阕
On our page we gong write
送千里无邪
I'll pray through the night
你就是梦浸白了新月
You're like the stars that light up my sky
才会有悲欢离合阴晴圆缺
Wish I could reach you but I'll never realize
你就是风染红了枫叶
You're like a storm that blows up my mind
才会让我的思念漫山遍野
I'm losing all control but I feel it's right
你就是泪浸白了初雪
You got my heart and soul electrified
才会如离人来去飘洒摇曳
I'm giving all my might dying to survive
你就是你染红了岁月
You cast a shadow right on my life
改变我黑白而无言的世界
Take all the rays of light to another side
如溪水潺潺淌过古街
Like standing on the end of a line
带走了如梦般的时节
Pride's hanging on the edge of your lies
小桥上人潮络绎不绝
Despite of all the times that I've tried
牵引我思绪层出不迭
You've fought so hard to keep me in line
若不识梁祝变成蝴蝶
I'll give you all that I have inside
驾紫烟穿过天上宫阙
I'll take you down to the paradise
绝不知人间多愁离别
My feelings for you can't be disguised
吹落叶散作秋风清切
I'm not the one you should left behind
将相思寄明月
Pray under the moonlight
心缱绻意难决
It takes time to get right
将此情置长夜
Will never compromise
似繁星明灭
Till stars come aline
你就是梦浸白了新月
You're like the stars that light up my sky
才会有悲欢离合阴晴圆缺
Wish I could reach you but I'll never realize
你就是风染红了枫叶
You're like a storm that blows up my mind
才会让我的思念漫山遍野
I'm losing all control but I feel it's right
你就是泪浸白了初雪
You got my heart and soul electrified
才会如离人来去飘洒摇曳
I'm giving all my might dying to survive
你就是你染红了岁月
You cast a shadow right on my life
改变我黑白而无言的世界
Take all the rays of light to another side
你就是梦浸白了新月
You're like the stars that light up my sky
才会有悲欢离合阴晴圆缺
Wish I could reach you but I'll never realize
你就是风染红了枫叶
You're like a storm that blows up my mind
才会让我的思念漫山遍野
I'm losing all control but I feel it's right
你就是泪浸白了初雪
You got my heart and soul electrified
才会如离人来去飘洒摇曳
I'm giving all my might dying to survive
你就是你染红了岁月
You cast a shadow right on my life
改变我黑白而无言的世界
Take all the rays of light to another side